Six dollars,please.
麻烦六块钱
Six? I just had it for one night. It's three.
六块？我才租了一个晚上 是三块钱
Eight o'clock's the cutoff. And,oh,it's 8:02.
八点钟结算，现在八点两分了
You know,in a weird way, you have too much power.
不知道为什么 你的权力好像太大了
You have to help me because I only have three.
你得帮帮我，我只有三块钱
I can help with that.
我可以帮忙
Oh,my God. Richard?
我的天，理查？
Your lip went bald.
你的胡子刮掉了
Thanks.
谢谢
You look great!
你气色很好
Right.
是啊
No,you do. You....
不，真的，你…
What?
什么？
You got panties stuck to your leg.
你的内裤黏在腿上了
I was just grabbing some things out of the dryer,and static cling.
我刚才从烘干机里 拿出衣服，这是静电
Or maybe God knew I'd be running into you and saw an opportunity.
也许老天爷知道我会碰到你 觉得这是个机会
It's good to see you.
见到你真高兴
It's good to see you too.
我也是
The One Where Monica and Rich are Just Friends
本集播出： “摩妮卡与查理成为朋友”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
See that guy? He's in "Classics" now...
看到那砘锩挥校 他现在看的是经典巨片
... but as soon as we leave, he's going straight to the porn.
不过等我们一走 他就马上去逛色情片
He'll go to the counter with Citizen Kane,Vertigo and Clockwork Orgy.
到时候他会租“大国民” “迷魂记”和“发条橘子”
This is nice.
这样真好
-I miss this. -Me too.
我好怀念这种时光 我也是
You want to get a hamburger or something?
想一起吃个汉堡什么的吗？
I don't know if that's a good idea.
我不知道这样好不好
Just friends. I won't grope you. I promise.
只是朋友嘛 我保证不会毛手毛脚
I think it's too soon.
我觉得太快了
No,it's not too soon. I had lunch at 11.
不会太快，我十一点吃的午餐
Yeah,baby!
好啊
-What are you making? -Chocolate milk. Want some?
你在做什么？ 巧克力牛奶，想喝吗？
No,thanks. I'm 29.
不，谢了，我已经29岁了
Oh,my God! I gotta go to work!
我的天，我得上班了
What time will you get off tonight?
你今晚几点下班？
It could be really late.
可能会很晚
Not again!
拜托，怎么又这样？
I know. I'm sorry. I'll make a deal with you,okay?
我知道，对不起 我们打个商量好吗？
Every night that you're asleep before I get home...
只要你在我回家以前睡着…
... I will wake you up in a way that has proved popular in the past.
我就用你以前 很喜欢的方法让你起来
Well,if you need to stay late, I want to be supportive of that.
如果你要加班 我很愿意支持你
Look at you. Since when do you rollerblade?
看，你什么时候开始溜冰了？
Since tomorrow.
明天
I met a cute guy in the park.
我在公园遇到一个帅哥
And he jogs and blades and swims and so we made a deal.
他是慢跑、溜冰和 游泳高手，我们说好了
He's gonna teach me how to do jock stuff.
他要教我各种运动
-And what are you gonna do for him? -I'm gonna let him.
那你要如何回报他？ 我会让他达到目的
Cool.
很好
Good morning.
早安
Somebody got in late last night.
有人昨晚很晚才回来哦
Yeah,well,I ran into Richard.
这个嘛，我碰到理查了
When did this happen?
什么时候的事？
Around 8:02.
大概八点两分
We talked for a while,and then we went out for an innocent burger.
我们聊了一会儿 然后一起吃了个单纯的汉堡
There's no such thing as an "innocent burger."
没有所谓“单纯的汉堡”
-Gonna see him again? -Tomorrow night.
你还会跟他见面吗？ 明天晚上
Monica,what are you doing?
摩妮卡，你这是在干什么？
She spent six months getting over him...
她花了六个月才忘记他…
...and now she's celebrating that by going on a date with him.
现在她庆祝的方式 就是跟他约会
It's not a date,okay?
这不是约会，好吗？
I'm teaching him how to make a lasagna for a potluck dinner.
我要教他做千层面 他要在家里请客
You might want to make extra,because you'll be hungry after the sex.
最好多做一点 做爱之后会很饿
We're not gonna have sex.
我们不会上床
Nothing's changed here. He still doesn't want children,and I still do.
一切如旧，他还是不要孩子 我还是想要孩子
So we're just gonna be friends.
所以我们只能当朋友
Naked friends.
赤裸裸的朋友
-Do you have any ice? -Check the freezer.
你有冰吗？ 打开冷冻库看看
If there's none in there, we're probably out.
如果没有，那大概就是用完了
Are you just getting home? It's late.
你刚下班吗？很晚了
I know. I had the greatest day,though.
我知道，不过今天实在太棒了
I went to a meeting with reps from Calvin Klein.
我和卡文克莱的销售代表开会
I liked a line of lingerie,so my boss ordered a ton of it. And you?
我看中一款性感内衣 我老板就订了一吨，你呢？
I discovered I'm able to count all my teeth using just my tongue.
我发现我可以 光用舌头数完所有牙齿
Why do you have a copy of The Shining in your freezer?
你把一本“鬼店” 放在冷冻库干嘛？
I was reading it last night and I got scared,so....
我昨晚越看越害怕，就…
But you're safe from it if it's in the freezer?
把书放进冷冻库 你就安全了吗？
Well,safer.
至少安全一点
I never start reading it...
我每次看书的时候…
...without making sure we got room in the freezer.
都先确定冰库里有地方放…
How often do you read it?
你常常看这本书吗？
Haven't you ever read a book over and over again?
你从不把一本书一看再看吗？
I read Little Women more than once.
“小妇人”我看了好几次
It's a classic. What's so great about The Shining?
那是经典作品 “鬼店”哪里好看？
The question should be,what is not so great about The Shining?
你应该问 “鬼店”有哪里不好看
And the answer would be, "nothing." All right?
答案是“没有”，知道吗？
This is the scariest book ever.
这是有史以来最恐怖的书
I bet it's better than that classic of yours.
一定比你的经典作品好看
We'll just see about that,okay?
我们走着瞧，好吗？
I will read The Shining, and you will read Little Women.
我看“鬼店” 你看“小妇人”
All right,you got it.
好，没问题
Now,Rach,these little women....
瑞秋，这些小妇人
How little are they?
到底有多小？
I mean,are they,like,scary little?
会不会很恐怖？
Chandler,Ross? This is Robert.
钱德、罗斯，这是劳勃
You have lipstick right here.
你这里沾了唇膏
That's okay,it's mine. We just kissed.
没关系，那是我的唇膏 我们刚才接吻了
Isn't it a bit cold out for shorts?
穿短裤有点冷吧？
Well,I'm from California.
我是加州人
Right. Sometimes you guys just burst into flame.
对，有时候你们加州人会自燃
I'm up. I'm up. I've gotten up now. Anybody want anything?
我起来了…我起来了 有人要什么吗？
-I'll have coffee. -Me too.
我要咖啡 我也是
Make that three.
三杯吧
Ross,why don't you come with me?
罗斯，跟我来
What's the matter? What's going on?
怎么了？怎么回事？
Robert's coming out.
劳勃快出来了
What do you mean? Is he gay?
什么意思？他是同性恋？
He's coming out of his shorts.
他就快从短裤里掉出来了
What?
什么？
The man is showing brain.
这砘锉┞吨匾部位
Are you sure? Hold on.
你确定？等一下
I'm sorry. That was a coffee and a....
对不起 你们点的是咖啡和…
Coffee. We could write it down.
咖啡，我们可以写下来
No,no. That won't be necessary.
不…不用了
Well?
怎么样？
What do we do? What do we do?
我们该怎么办？…
Well,I suppose we just try to not look directly at it.
我想只能尽量不要用正眼看
Like an eclipse.
就像日食一样
When people compliment my cooking tonight,what do I say?
如果今晚有人称赞我的手艺 我该怎么说？
You say,"Thank you." Then you buy me something pretty.
你说“多谢夸奖” 然后买礼物酬谢我
Come on,we're gonna put our hands in this bowl...
来，我们把手放进这个里…
...and we're gonna start squishing the tomatoes.
然后开始把番茄压碎
This feels very weird.
感觉怪怪的
You touch people's eyeballs and this feels weird?
你整天摸人家的眼球 还说这感觉怪怪的？
Sure,I touch them. But I spent years learning not to squish them.
我当然会摸人家的眼球 但我好不容易才不动手压碎
That's my hand.
那是我的手
-Keep squishing. -The tomatoes are squishing.
继续压 番茄吱吱响
You got some on your shirt.
你的衬衫沾到了
Hold on a second.
等一下
Just put a little club soda on it. Get to it right away.
马上放苏打水上去
It should do...
应该…
...the trick.
就可以了
What?
怎么了？
You've got some on your pants.
你裤子上也沾到了
I'll just throw them out.
干脆丢掉算了
These little women!
这些小妇人
You're liking it?
你喜欢吗？
Oh,yeah. Amy just burned Jo's manuscript.
喜欢，爱美刚烧了乔的稿子
I don't see how he could forgive her.
我看他永远不会原谅她
Jo's a girl. It's short for Josephine.
乔是女的，是约瑟芬的简称
But Jo's got a crush on Laurie.
但乔喜欢劳瑞
You mean it's like a girl-girl thing?
你是说这是女同性恋？
That is the one thing missing from The Shining.
“鬼店”可没有这种东西
No,actually,Laurie's a boy.
不，其实劳瑞是男的
No wonder Rachel had to read this so many times.
难怪瑞秋要看这么多次
How'd the basketball go?
篮球好玩吗？
I learned how to shoot a lay-up, a foul shot,and a 23-pointer.
我学会了篮板球、罚球 和23分球
You mean a 3-pointer?
你是说三分球吧？
I get more because I'm dainty.
我姿势优美，可以多几分
Is there a phone here to check my messages?
这里有没有电话可以查留言？
-ln back. Do you want a quarter? -I always carry one in my sock.
在后面，你有铜板吗？ 我一向在袜子里放一个铜板
What are you doing? Get back on your side
你干嘛？回去那边坐
Hello!
哈罗
I'm Joey. We haven't met.
我是乔伊，我们还没见过面
Good to meet you. Robert.
很高兴认识你，劳勃
What?
怎么了？
What? You guys,what is going on?
怎么了？你们怎么回事？
Do you not like Robert?
你们不喜欢劳勃吗？
Why are you laughing?
你们笑什么？
Calm down. No reason to get testy.
平静一点，用不着激动
-You guys! Come on! -We're sorry.
你们怎么回事嘛？ 对不起
It just seems that Robert isn't as concealed in the shorts area...
只不过你的劳勃的短裤 蔽体的的部份…
...as one may have hoped.
好像是少了一点
What do you mean?
什么意思？
Could you pass me those cookies?
把饼干拿给我好吗？
Sure.
没问题
So how'd the lasagna go over?
他们喜不喜欢千层面？
Really? Good. So you owe me three pretty things.
真的？很好 现在你欠我三样礼物了
I've been thinking about you too.
我一直在想着你的事
Well,no. It's hard, this "platonomy" thing.
不，这种柏拉图恋情很不容易
It's a word.
这是一个词
I do think it's better this way. We're being smart.
我觉得这样比较好 这样才是明智之举
Yes,I'm sure.
对，我肯定
You really sure?
你真的肯定？
I'll call you back.
我再回你电话
So we can be friends who sleep together.
我们可以当有性关系的朋友
Absolutely. This'll just be something we do.
没错，这不代表什么
Like racquetball.
就像打壁球一样
Sounds smart and healthy to me.
我觉得聪明又健康
So just out of curiosity...
不过基于好奇心
...do you currently have any other "racquetball" buddies?
你还有几个打壁球的伙伴？
Just your dad.
只有你爸爸一个
Although that's actually racquetball.
虽然那是真的壁球
You know,I do have a blind date...
我下星期二…
...with my sister's neighbor next Tuesday.
要和我妹妹的邻居约会
Do you want me to cancel it?
你希望我取消吗？
No!
不要
Because if you did, that means you'd be canceling for me.
如果你取消 那就是为我取消的
-And we're just friends. -Exactly.
而我们只是朋友 没错
Oh,don't sit down.
不要坐
-Ready to go? -You bet.
可以走了吗？ 可以
And first,here's a gift.
不过先送你一个礼物
Stretchy pants?!
伸缩内裤？
The greatest things in the world! If I were you,I'd wear them every day.
这个东西好得要命 如果是我，我会天天穿
Gee,thank you. Really,that's so nice.
谢谢，真的，你太体帖了
But,to be honest, I don't think I can wear these.
不过说老实话 我看我不能穿
They're so tight. I'd feel like I'm on display.
太紧了，我会觉得 好像是给人家看的
I'm sorry.
对不起
That's all right. I'll figure....
没关系，我再想办法…
How's it going?
大家好吗？
Good.
很好
How's The Shining?
“鬼店”好不好看？
Danny just went into Room 217.
丹尼刚走进217号房
The next part's the best! That dead lady in the bathtub
下面是最精彩的 浴缸里的死女人…
You're gonna ruin it!
这样就不好看了
I'll talk in code.
我用密码说
Remember when the kid sees those two "blanks" in the hallway?
记得小孩在走廊 看到那两个“空白”吗？
Yeah,that's very cool.
对，那里很好看
All "blank" and no "blank" makes "blank" a "blank-blank."
所有的“空白”都把 “空白”弄成“空白”
No,the end!
不，讲结局
Jack almost kills them with the "blank"...
杰克差点用“空白” 杀了他们
... but in the last second, they get away.
不过到最后关头 他们还是跑了
I can't believe you just did that.
你居然做这种事
I can't believe she cracked your code.
她居然识破你的密码
Okay. Laurie proposes to Jo and she says no...
好，劳瑞跟乔求婚，她拒绝了
...even though she's in love with him. Then he ends up marrying Amy.
虽然她其实爱着他 他后来娶了爱美
Mine was by accident!
我不是存心要讲的
The boiler explodes and destroys the hotel and kills the dad.
锅炉爆炸，烧毁旅馆 那个爸爸也被烧死了
Beth dies.
贝丝死了
Beth dies?
贝丝死了？
Is that true? If I keep reading,is Beth gonna die?
真的吗？如果继续看下去 贝丝就会死？
No,Beth doesn't die. She doesn't die. Does she,Rachel?
不，贝丝不会死，她不会死 对不对，瑞秋？
He's asking if you've ruined...
他问的是你是不是破坏了
...the first book he's ever loved that didn't star Jack Nicholson.
他喜欢的第一本不是由 杰克尼克逊当主角的小说？
No. She doesn't die.
不，她不会死
Then why would you say that?
那你干嘛这么说？
Because I wanted to hurt you.
因为我故意要伤害你
Oh,there they are. I dropped my keys.
在这里，我的钥匙掉了
Got them.
找到了
Sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起，对不起
You would not believe my day.
你一定不敢相信我今天有多惨
I had to work two shifts. And then to top it off...
我上了两个班 除此之外…
... I lost one of my fake boobs in a grill fire.
我的义乳又被烤炉的火烧了
What are you smiling at?
你在笑什么？
I was thinking your day could still pick up.
我在想可能会柳暗花明又一村
I love this "friend" thing!
我喜欢这种朋友关系
Robert's gonna be here any second, so could one of you just tell him?
劳勃马上就要来了 你们哪个人跟他说好吗？
Please,right now.
拜托，马上说
Every time I see him,it's "ls it on the loose? Is it watching me?"
我一见他就想“那玩意儿 是不是晃来晃去看着我”
We can't tell him.
我们不能跟他说
You can't go up to a guy you barely know and talk about his "stuff."
你不能跟素昧平生的人 谈他的“那话儿”
He's right. Even if it's to say something complimentary.
他说得对 就算是赞美也不行
You ready for the gym?
可以去健身房了吗？
There's a new rock-climbing wall. We can spot each other.
有一面新的攀岩墙 我们可以互相侦查
Yeah,I can spot you from here.
我从这里就可以侦查你
What?
什么？
Listen,Robert....
听我说，劳勃
Hey,don't we have to...?
我们不是要…
Yeah,we got....
对，我们要
I think you're really,really great.
我觉得你这个人真的很棒
Oh,God. Here we go again.
老天，又来了
Why does this keep happening? Is it something I'm putting out there?
为什么老是发生这种事？ 我什么东西让你不高兴？
Is this my fault? Or am I just nuts?
这是我的错吗？
I don't know what to say.
我不知道该怎么说
Hey,buddy? This is a family place. Put the mouse back in the house.
老弟？这是阖家光临的地方 把老鼠放回屋里去
Really? It's just like everyone else's apartment.
真的？这间公寓很普通啊
It's got rooms and walls and ceilings.
一样有房间、墙壁和天花板
I just wanted to see where you live. Now give me the tour.
我只是想看看你住的地方 带我参观参观
Oh,my God!
我的天
-This is the living room. -That's nice.
这里是客厅 真舒适
-And this is the kitchen. -That's real pretty.
这里是厨房 真漂亮
Wait a minute. Don't I get to see the bedroom?
等一下 我不能参观卧室吗？
Well,it's pretty much your typical...
这是很普通的…
... bedroom.
卧室
We're still on this side of the door. I didn't get to see it.
我们还在门的这一头 我还没看到
Oh,shoot. Maybe next time. Thanks for a lovely evening.
要命，下次吧 今晚非常愉快
So who is she?
她是谁？
That was the blind date I told you about.
我跟你说过 就是我妹妹介绍的人
She called and switched it from Tuesday.
她打电话来改期到今天
Did you like her?
你喜欢她吗？
I'm just asking as a friend, because I am totally fine with this.
我是以朋友的身份问的 因为我不会不高兴
Well,you seem fine.
你看起来很高兴
Okay,you know what? I'm not fine. I'm not.
好，你知道吗？ 我不高兴，我很不高兴
I mean,how could I be fine? Hearing you come in with her.
我怎么高兴得起来？ 听到你跟她进来
She wants to see your bedroom.
她还想参观你的卧室
You know what?
你知道吗？
What if we're friends...
我们或许可以做朋友…
...who don't see other people?
但不跟其他人交往
You mean "exclusive" friends?
你是说“专属的”朋友？
Why not?
有何不可？
I mean,this has been the most amazing week.
我是说，这个星期美好极了
Would it be so terrible?
这也没什么不好吧
Even if we were friends who lived together?
我们还可以一面做朋友 一面住在一起
Or maybe someday,friends who stood up in front of their other friends...
或许有一天 可以站在其他朋友面前
...and vowed to be friends forever.
发誓当一辈子的朋友
You know,we're back where we were.
我们又回到原点了
Honey,I would love to do all that, but nothing's changed.
亲爱的，我求之不得 但一切都没有改变
That's not true. You don't have a moustache.
不是这样的 你把胡子刮掉了
Okay,one thing's changed.
好吧，有一件事改变了
But we still want different things, and we know how this is gonna end.
但我们生活目标仍不同 我们都知道结局会怎么样
You know what?
你知道吗？
I gotta walk out of here right now.
我得马上离开这个房间
Because getting over you is the hardest thing I have ever had to do.
因为忘记你是我一生中 最不容易的一件事
I don't think I could do it again.
我想我再也做不到了
I know I couldn't.
我知道我做不到
How about one last game of racquetball?
再打最后一场壁球怎么样？
Watch the thorns!
小心玫瑰刺
What?
怎么了？
Beth is really,really sick.
贝丝病得很重很重
Jo's there,but I don't think there's anything she can do.
乔在陪她 但我想她也没办法
You wanna put the book in the freezer?
你要把书放在冰库里吗？